export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Javascript',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 4,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the color "rosso" in English?',
      choices: ['Red', 'Blue', 'Yellow', 'Green'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Red',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "grazie" in English?',
      choices: ['Please', 'Sorry', 'Thank you', 'Excuse me'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Thank you',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the capital of Italy?',
      choices: ['Milan', 'Rome', 'Naples', 'Florence'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Rome',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "ciao" mean in English?',
      choices: ['Goodbye', 'Hello', 'Thank you', 'How are you'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Hello',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the author of "La Divina Commedia"?',
      choices: ['Leonardo da Vinci', 'Michelangelo', 'Dante Alighieri', 'Giovanni Boccaccio'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Dante Alighieri',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you say "amore" in English?',
      choices: ['Love', 'Friend', 'Family', 'Home'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Love',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the day before "venerdì"?',
      choices: ['Lunedì', 'Martedì', 'Mercoledì', 'Giovedì'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Giovedì',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "buongiorno" mean in English?',
      choices: ['Goodbye', 'Good morning', 'Good evening', 'Good night'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Good morning',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the official language spoken in Italy?',
      choices: ['French', 'Spanish', 'English', 'Italian'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Italian',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the famous monument in Pisa?',
      choices: ['Eiffel Tower', 'Leaning Tower of Pisa', 'Colosseum', 'Milan Cathedral'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Leaning Tower of Pisa',
    },
  ],
}